Library. University Librarian. Administrative files UARC.0377
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Space Planning, 1989-1990; 890267 (Box 419, Folder 18)
- Special Collections includes Annual Reports and Discussion Group, 1988-1993 (Box 419, Folder 19-20)
- Special Funds, 1991-1993; 890266 (Box 419, Folder 21)
- SRLF (Southern Regional Library Facility)Annual Reports; Boards; Operations and Planning; Reconversion, 1988-1993; 890265 (Box 420, Folder 1-6)
- Stack Annex, 1980-1987; 890263 (Box 420, Folder 7)
- Statistics; Circulation; Functional Analysis; Library Statistical Reports; Questionnaires, Reprographic; User Surveys, 1988-1997; 890262 (Box 420, Folder 8-23)
- Stevenson Archive, 1990-1991; 890260 (Box 420, Folder 24)
- Strategic Planning Committee (UCLA), 1989; 890258 (Box 420, Folder 25)
- Sun Proposal, 1992-1993; 890259 (Box 420, Folder 26)
- Task Force, 1985-1992; 890257 (Box 421, Folder 1-2)
- Taxes, 1991-1992; 890256 (Box 421, Folder 3)
- Technical Services, 1989-1990; 890250 (Box 421, Folder 4)
- Title VI, 1991; 890249 (Box 421, Folder 5)
- UC (University of California) CDC (Collection Development Committee, 1991-1993 and 1996; 890248 (Box 421, Folder 6)
- University of California/UCLA ILL Reports: Hughes and Steel, 1994-1996; 890245 (Box 421, Folder 7-8)
- University of California Library Statistics, 1989-1991; 890244 (Box 421, Folder 9)
- University of California (Non-UC), 1988; 890243 (Box 421, Folder 10)
- Undergraduate Education, 1992; 890247 (Box 421, Folder 11)
- University Elementary School Cataloging Statistics, 1990-1992; 890242 (Box 421, Folder 12)
- University Research Library, Miscellaneous, 1984-1992; 890241 (Box 421, Folder 13)
- US Newspaper Program Resource Notebook, 1990; 890240 (Box 421, Folder 14)
- Visitors, 1991-1992; 890239 (Box 421, Folder 15)
- Women's Studies, 1989-1990; 890238 (Box 421, Folder 16)
- Academic Salary Scales, 1987-1988; 890237 (Box 421, Folder 17)
- Administrative Services Retreat, 1993; 890236 (Box 421, Folder 18)
- Arts and Architecture Libraries Consolidation, 1991; 890233 (Box 421, Folder 19)
- Books and Bindery Expenses for Auditor, 1987-1988; 890235 (Box 421, Folder 20)
- Bruman Library Miscellaneous and Statistics, 1962-1967; 890234 (Box 421, Folder 21)
- Budgets including Materials; Library Pre-Fiscal Close Financial Review; Savings and Ideas, 890232 (Box 421, Folder 22-27)
- California Library Networking Task Force, 1989-1990; 890231 (Box 421, Folder 28-29)
- Academic Technology Center, 993; 890230 (Box 422, Folder 1)
- ALA Collection Development, 1993; 890229 (Box 422, Folder 2)
- Audio-Visual Services, 1992-1993; 890228 (Box 422, Folder 3)
- Caldwell Collection, 1993; 890197 (Box 422, Folder 4)
- California Multitype Library Network (California Library Networking Task Force), 1990-1993; 890224 (Box 422, Folder 5)
- CALLS Linking Project, 1993; 890185 (Box 422, Folder 6)
- Cataloging Department and Statistics, 1993; 890225 (Box 422, Folder 7-8)
- Center for 17th and 18th Century Studies Faculty Advisory Committee, 1985-1990; 890222 (Box 422, Folder 9-10)
- Chicano Studies Research Center Library and Chicano/Latino Net, 1989-1993; 890227 (Box 422, Folder 11)
- China and China-Fudan, 1988-1993; 890226 (Box 422, Folder 12-13)
- CLASS (Cooperative Library Agency for Systems and Services), 1993; 890219 (Box 422, Folder 14)
- Coalition for Networked Information, 1990-1993; 890216 (Box 422, Folder 15-16)
- Collection Development Council, 1993; 890220 (Box 422, Folder 17)
- College of Letters and Science, 1989-1993.; 890206 (Box 422, Folder 18)
- Compacting the URL Card Catalog, 1990-1992; 890204 (Box 422, Folder 19)
- CONSER Program, 1992-1993; 890218 (Box 422, Folder 20)
- Cooperative Agreements-UC, 1993; 890217 (Box 422, Folder 21)
- Corporate Affiliates, 1991-1992; 890205 (Box 422, Folder 22)
- Council of Chancellors, 1989; 890031 (Box 422, Folder 23)
- Council on Library Resources, 1990-1991; 890030 (Box 422, Folder 24)
- Dance Department, Includes Dance Sources, 1990-1993; 890202 (Box 422, Folder 25)
- Digital Library Initiative, 1993; 890203 (Box 422, Folder 26)
- East Asian Library (Rudolph), 1993; 890201 (Box 422, Folder 27)
- ECIIG (Electronic Government Information Initiatives Group--UC/Stanford) and Library (GIL), 1995-1998; 890200 (Box 422, Folder 28)
- Electronic Resources, 1993; 890199 (Box 422, Folder 29)
- Equipment: DASD; Optical and Images; Public Printers, 1991-1993; 890198 (Box 422, Folder 30)
- Full-Text Electronic Resources, 1993; 890196 (Box 423, Folder 1)
- Germanic, 1993; 890195 (Box 423, Folder 2)
- Heads of Technical Services, 1993; 890194 (Box 423, Folder 3)
- Hoffberg Collection of Artists Books, 1985, 1993; 890193 (Box 423, Folder 4)
- Imaging, 1993; 890192 (Box 423, Folder 5)
- Info Technology Group, 1991-1993; 890191 (Box 423, Folder 6)
- InfoUCLA, 1993-1995; 890190 (Box 423, Folder 7)
- Inter library Loan (ILL), 1992-1993; 890189 (Box 423, Folder 8)
- Journal Article Database Task Force, 1989-1993; 890188 (Box 423, Folder 9)
- Korean American Research Project, 1993; 890187 (Box 423, Folder 10)
- LA Bookfest, 1992; 890186 (Box 423, Folder 11)
- Lantz Collection, 1993; 890184 (Box 423, Folder 12)
- Latin America/Hispanic American Periodicals Index (HAPI), 1993; 890183 (Box 423, Folder 13)
- Library Automation Review Committee (LARC), 1986-1989; 890182 (Box 423, Folder 14-15)
- Library Associates, 1993; 890181 (Box 423, Folder 16)
- Library of Congress Cooperative Cataloging Council Task Force, 1993; 890180 (Box 423, Folder 17)
- Math Reading Room, 1989; 890179 (Box 423, Folder 18)
- Orion 2, 1993; 890178 (Box 423, Folder 19)
- Powell Library Shared Processing Facility, 1992-1993; 890176 (Box 423, Folder 20)
- Preservation Including Annual Report, 1992-1994; 890175 (Box 423, Folder 21)
- Price Increase Justification, 1993-1994; 890174 (Box 423, Folder 22)
- Psychology Serials, 1993; 890173 (Box 423, Folder 23)
- Public Affairs Services (PAS), 1993; 890172 (Box 423, Folder 24)
- Public Information Electronic Kiosks, 1993; 890171 (Box 423, Folder 25)
- Sales Tax Recovery, 1993; 890170 (Box 423, Folder 26)
- Science Engineering Library (SEL)/PSTL, 1991-1994; 890169 (Box 423, Folder 27)
- Scherrei, Rita, 1990-1991; 890146 (Box 424, Folder 1)
- Senate (Academic) Committee on Libraries Minutes, 1993; 890168 (Box 424, Folder 2)
- Serials prices., 1989-1992.; 890177 (Box 422, Folder 3)
- Shared Collections and Access Program (SCAP), 1992-1993; 890166 (Box 424, Folder 4)
- Slavic, 1992-1993; 890165 (Box 424, Folder 5)
- Social Sciences and Social Science Computing Facility, 1988-1993; 890164 (Box 424, Folder 6)
- South Asia Cooperation/Consortium (SACWEST), 1992-1993; 890163 (Box 424, Folder 7)
- Space Planning, 1993; 890162 (Box 424, Folder 8)
- Spingarn Collection (Library Special Collections), 1993; 890161 (Box 424, Folder 9)
- Statistics (Undergraduate Library-UGLI), 1991-1992; 890160 (Box 424, Folder 10)
- Sun Proposal, 1992-1993; 890157 (Box 424, Folder 11)
- Task Force, 1993-1996; 890154 (Box 424, Folder 12)
- Task Force on Inter Campus Programs and Distance Learning, 1993; 890152 (Box 424, Folder 13)
- URL/YRL Media Installation Budget, 1993; 890151 (Box 424, Folder 14)
- Women's Studies, 1993; 890150 (Box 424, Folder 15)
- Windows Project/Asset Source for Software Engineering Technology (ASSET), 1993; 890149 (Box 424, Folder 16)
- Z39.50 Project, 1993; 890148 (Box 424, Folder 17)
- UCLA Library Visitors, 1964-1985 (Box 425)